nsgp.org 2005-04-04

# MembersFirst Privacy Statement

MembersFirst, Inc. is committed to respecting your privacy. We've structured our website so that, in general, you can visit your club on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with MembersFirst, Inc. 

This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers four main areas: Awareness, Choice, Security, and Oversight. 

**Awareness**  
MembersFirst, Inc. provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every MemberFirst client webpage. 

**What we collect**  
On some client web pages you can make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name and contact information. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our services, and contact preferences. 

**How we use it**  
MembersFirst, Inc. uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a service, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize our web site for you. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. We will also follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable. 

**Who we share it with**  
MembersFirst, Inc. will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other member entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf to complete the activities described above. Such member entities and/or business partners, including those located in other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data. 

**Choice**  
MembersFirst, Inc. will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.. 

**Security**  
MembersFirst, Inc. is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Oversight**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact [TechnicalSupport@memfirst.com](mailto:TechnicalSupport@memfirst.com)

**Copyright ©2004-2005 MembersFirst, Inc. All rights reserved.**
